https://www.learninglinks.org.au/privacy-policy/

StrategyOur ImpactAnnual ReportsServices
Children & YouthNDIS ServicesAssessmentsEarly InterventionTelehealth and Online ServicesSpeech TherapyOccupational TherapySpecialist TutoringPsychological TherapyPsychology Group ProgramsSchool Holiday ProgramsSchool Transitions and ReadinessPrep 4 Preschool PlaygroupPreschoolOut of School Hours Care
Parents, Carers & Families
Parenting Programs
Parent & Child Programs
Counselling
Professionals & Schools
School Referrals
Professional Development Courses
School Programs
Opportunities to make a differenceOur Recruitment Process
Psychologist Registration ProgramVision, Mission & ValuesContactCartStaff Login Member Login
Shop
Subscribe
Donate Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyLearning Links is committed to respecting and preserving the confidentiality of information acquired and not releasing any such information to third parties without proper authority.In order that Learning Links can maintain privacy in the workplace it is important for staff to know what information may be collected and retained by Learning Links and whether it can be passed on to others.This policy outlines:The kinds of personal information we collect and holdHow we collect, hold, and keep information secureThe purposes for which we collect, hold, use, and disclose informationYour right to access and seek correction of informationHow you may complain about privacy matters. Download the full Privacy Policy Download the Easy Read Privacy PolicyServicesRECENT ARTICLES
How to prepare your child for starting schoolThe transition from preschool to 'big school’ is a huge milestone. Here are some tips to help prepare your child for starting school.Thursday, 10th December 2020
Read More
Mila’s story – Dancing Queen Mila is 4 years old and has Down Syndrome. In 2020 Mila started attending Learning Links Preschool, where she receives support and individualised care. Mila’s mum and dad spoke to Learning Links about what Learning Links Preschool means for Mila’s education.   This story was written by Mila’s mum and dad.  Mila was diagnosed with Down Syndrome... Read MoreThursday, 3rd December 2020
Read More
Digital education for children and teachers Across 2020 Learning Links was able to offer 652 children, teaches and families online digital programs and workshops, the most amount of digital services ever offered by Learning Links in one single year.  Thursday, 12th November 2020
Read More
Promoting resilience in the classroomThe best way to promote resilience in the classroom is to foster positive relationships while modelling and teaching some simple social and emotional skills.Wednesday, 11th November 2020
Read More
Shop
Subscribe
Donate
Home
Our Story
Our Services
News &
Events
Resources
Get Involved
Feedback and Complaints
Quality and improvement is important to Learning Links. If you would like to provide feedback or raise a complaint please
Contact us.
Support Office
Suite 3, Level 1140 Bourke Rd
PO Box 6282
Alexandria NSW 2015
Telephone: 1300 003 900
mail@learninglinks.org.au
Charity Housie
For venues, sessions,and details click
Feedback & Complaints |
Whistleblower Policy×Subscribe to Learning LinksIn our free monthly eNewsletter you’ll receive interesting articles on education and learning, tips for supporting children, our latest service offerings and programs, news, events and volunteer opportunities.
Contact TypeParentProfessionalSupporter
×
Read more
